http://www.bhrentacar.com/page/privacy_policy.html

Privacy Policy - Beverly Hills Car Rental
We are taking all precautionary measures to combat the spread of the COVID-19 virus as set forth by the Centers for Disease Control (CDC) and The World Health Organization (WHO) in the interest of the health of our clients and staff.
We are open for business and ready to serve you The premier luxury and exotic car rental company The premier luxury and exotic car rental company
EnglishSpanishChineseJapaneseKoreanItalianFrenchArabicGermanRussian
Intl. 310-448-2018
310-448-2018  Intl.
EnglishSpanishChineseJapaneseKoreanItalianFrenchArabicGermanRussian
Home | Vehicles | Reservations | Contact
Exotic Prestige Convertible Luxury SUV Hybrid Standard Van
Mercedes- Bentley- Lamborghini Ferrari- Porsche- Rolls Royce -
OtherAcuraAston MartinAudiBentleyBMWCadillacChevroletFerrariFordJeepLamborghiniLexusLincolnMaseratiMercedesMcLarenPorscheRange RoverRolls RoyceTeslaToyota
Privacy Policy Statement for luxuryline.comFor each visitor to our Web pages, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online and have taken steps to protect the information you share with us.Luxury Line does collect certain user-specific information in order to provide you with customized services and content. Some personal information is gathered when you register to receive certain Luxury Line rental services or products. We may also ask you for personal information at other times, for example when you enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion. The better we know you, the better we can tailor our services to meet your needs.We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Luxury Line, or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service on this Web site; (d) to provide you with the services or products requested by you and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; or (e) to operate Luxury Line’s systems properly. We may also share your personal information with a sponsor or other third party who is interested in serving you (“Third-Party Providers”). You may inform us at any time not to share your personal information with such Third Party Providers by contacting us.Luxury Line reserves the right to change this statement at any time by posting revisions on the Luxury Line Web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. This privacy policy may apply to other Luxury Line products and services.
Beverly Hills Near Wilshire & Santa Monica(310) 274-69699732 S. Santa Monica Blvd.Beverly Hills, CA 90210 InformationAboutRental FAQRental PoliciesRental RequirementsPrivacy Policy LanguageEnglishSpanishChineseJapaneseKoreanItalianFrenchArabicGermanRussian Social Media point camera
